I'm gonna run to the store.
I'll pick you up when you're done.
(Sheldon:)Okay. I like it a little better
when you stay, but all right.
- Hey, Sheldon.
- Hello.
(Sheldon:)I'm here for my haircut
with Mr. D'Onofrio.
I'm sorry, Uncle Tony is in the hospital.
He's pretty sick.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear, Mr. D'Onofrio's
in the hospital.
(Sheldon:)Why do these things
always happen to me?
- l can cut it for you.
- You're not Mr. D'Onofrio.
l get my hair cut by Mr. D'Onofrio.
(Sheldon:)You believe this guy?
(Leonard:)Excuse us for a second.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, it's okay, he can do it.
He's a barber.
(Sheldon:)He's not a barber, he's the nephew.
An example of the nepotism...
(Sheldon:)...that runs rampant
in the barbering industry.
(Sheldon:)Besides Mr. D'Onofrio knows exactly
how I like my hair done...
(Sheldon:)...because he has all my haircut records
from my barber in Texas.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)When I first moved here, I was nervous
about finding a new barber...
(Sheldon:)...so my mother had all my haircut
records sent here to Mr. D'Onofrio.